bandung-flasher.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Bandung-Flasher.com GSM CDMA Cell Phone Repair Forum

| 

**Privacy Policy** Your privacy is important to us. We believe that by respecting your privacy we will earn the opportunity to build a lasting relationship with your business, your clients and your staff. Any information you provide to us will only be used for the purpose for which it was submitted. We collect your information primarily for proof, contact and billing purposes. Under no circumstances will your information be shared with, or sold to, or disclosed to any third party, except where required by law. 

This Privacy Policy applies only to information gathered in connection with Bandung-Flasher Forum consumer credit card accounts used for transactions at Bandung-Flasher Forum and applications for those accounts. 

In order to enhance our ability to provide you with the best services, opportunities, and choices possible, we collect, use, and share certain information about you. This policy explains what information we collect, with whom we share it with. The practices described in this policy are applicable to current and former customers and consumers who do business with us. The policy also explains how we protect the security and confidentiality of our customer information. 

**Information we collect and sources of information.**  
We may collect information about some of your personal details and documents, (such as, address, copy of credit card statements, identification, etc) all to help us process the order in which you've made, and for us to assure and prove that you are the person paying for the products. 

**Information we share with service providers or joint marketers.**  
We may disclose some of the information we collect, to companies that perform services on our behalf, including those who assist us in selling, billing, shipping and responding to customer inquiries. We may provide that information to others who perform marketing services for us and to financial institutions with whom we jointly offer financial products or services, subject to any requirements and restrictions of applicable state law. 

**Security and confidentiality of your information.**  
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know in order to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal and state law standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

**Order and Credit Card Information**

Bandung-Flasher Forum uses PayPal, a third-party provider of e-commerce solutions, to power the Bandung-Flasher store and in doing so, collects information about users, including credit card information. When a user purchases a membership from the Bandung-Flasher store, PayPal provides information about the customer, including name, address and email address, to Bandung-Flasher Forum. Bandung-Flasher Forum uses this information as set out in the end user agreement, agreed to by purchasers at the time of purchase. In particular, Bandung-Flasher Forum uses the information to license the software to you, support the software and send you information about updates, upgrades and new works or services provided by Bandung-Flasher Forum

PayPal requests information from the user on the order form, viewed by the user as a page hosted on the PayPal web server. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used as explained above. For example, if we have trouble processing an order, contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

Your credit card information does not pass through the PayPal sites under the terms of Bandung-Flasher Forum’s agreement with PayPal. PayPal does not share credit card information with Bandung-Flasher Forum. PayPal keeps your credit card information confidential and protects your credit card information through the use of industry-standard Secure Sockets (SSL) encryption technology.  
  
---
